Kristian Pospis

Web Developer Multimedia Designer



PROFILE

I am a 22 year old web developer and multimedia designer. I have a passion for designing logos and creating identities through branding and creating web designs. Web development allows me to create something new that could potentionally help others while designing fulfils my creative thrist. I have spent the last 4 years studying web design and development in Odense, Denmark. The courses are structured around group projects where students have to solve tasks while new teams are formed every month. The group projects have made me a better team player but I can handle a project on my own as well. I am a perfectionist when it comes to design and a pragmatic thinker when it comes to programming. I like to double check my work and make sure that everything I create is up to modern standards.

CONTACT



Phone 00 45 25 13 27 87



Email

kristian.pospis@gmail.com



Address

31 Hamburgerstrasse Heide, Schleswig Holstein Germany



Web Portfolio pospisk.me

EDUCATION

2010-2015

Sukromne Bilingvalne Gymnasium Galanta

The school was focused on English and some subjects such as history were taught in English. During the beginning of my education, our timetable was 60% English lessons, later it was reduced and I spruced up my German grammar.

2015-2017

(EAL) Multimedia design and communication AP degree

Since I was 10 years old I have played around with Photoshop and after finishing highschool, I wanted to study what I enjoyed doing in my freetime. When I have found a good school in Denmark I decided to move and learn more.

2017-2019

(UCL) Web development Bc degree

After receiving my AP degree I wanted to combine my design knowledge with web development, so that I could create intuitive UI/UX designs, frontend tools/plugins and interactive content.

EXPERIENCE

2017.02 - 2017.06 Internship

WITT-GRUPPE

During my studies at MMD EAL I have interned at the Witt-Gruppe in Weiden, Germany as a web designer for 4 months. I was working 37 hours per week and gaining knowledge from my experienced co-workers.

2018.08 - 2018.11 Internship

LISA.SK

During my studies at Web Dev UCL I have interned at Lisa.sk which is a slovakian web development company who provides the region and it's cities with governent websites. I have learned more about web development best practices and found myself as a frontend developer

LANGUAGES

English C1 HTML / CSS

German B2 JavaScript

Slovak (native) C# / .Net

Czech (70%) PHP

Hungarian (native) ... love to learn more!